# **Ceres Cook** (612) 501-1154

### **Management and Inventory Operator**

ceres.markley@gmail.com

#### **About Me**

I'm a seasoned management professional who is passionate about **problem-solving**, teamwork, and continued learning. During my experiences, I've cultivated my strengths in **developmental planning**, **project management**, and **leadership**. In my free time, I'm often listening to music, gaming, and trying new restaurants.

#### **Experience**

## Area Manager L5



Amazon @ Columbus, OH (2021-2023)

Responsible for creating and executing weekly site plans, maintaining a high-functioning Amazon site, management development, and analyzing inventory data reports to proactively drive reduction regarding inventory loss/waste costs.

# Amazon Fresh Assistant Shift Manager



Amazon @ Columbus, OH (2019-2021)

Responsible for running and maintaining a high-functioning Amazon site, management development and coaching, and conducting audits of warehouse performance to ensure goals are achieved.

#### **Full-Time On Road Shift Assistant**



Amazon @ Eagan, MN (2019)

Responsible for coordinating Delivery Associate (DA) training, mentoring associates, leading daily kick-off meetings, and ensuring successful area performance through tracking & metrics.

#### **Education**

**B.A.** Arts & Science

Inver Grove CC (2011-2012) Completed 30 Credits Computer Science **B.A.** Arts & Science

Bemidji State University (2011-2012) Completed 30 Credits Political Science